// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "In the movie 'Zootopia', what type of animal is the main character, Judy Hopps? ",
    answer: "Rabbit",
    options: [
      "Rabbit",
      "Monkey",
      "Squirrel",
      "Cat"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Who portraits the main character of the movie 'Mission Impossible'?",
    answer: "Tom Cruise",
    options: [
      "Esai Morales",
      "Tom Cruise",
      "Simon Pegg",
      "Johnny Depp"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Who directed the 'Avatar' Movie?",
    answer: "James Cameron",
    options: [
      "Tim Burton",
      "James Cameron",
      "Ridley Scott",
      "Peter Jackson"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Who plays the role of 'Jack Sparrow'?",
    answer: "Johnny Depp",
    options: [
      "Tom Cruise",
      "Leonardo dicaprio",
      "Tom Holland",
      "Johnny Depp"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "In the movie 'Frozen', what is the name of the snowman character?",
    answer: "Olaf",
    options: [
      "Genie",
      "Hei hei",
      "Olaf",
      "Pua"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is the house of Harry Potter?",
    answer: "Gryffindor",
    options: [
      "Gryffindor",
      "Ravenclaw",
      "Hufflepuff",
      "Slytherin"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "In which movie can you find T.Rex dinosaur?",
    answer: "Jurrasic Park",
    options: [
      "Pirates of the caribbean",
      "Fast and Furious",
      "Avatar",
      "Jurrasic Park"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "How many Golden Tickets are waiting to be found in Charlie and the Chocolate Factory?",
    answer: "5",
    options: [
      "10",
      "4",
      "5",
      "3"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which movie has Will Smith played in?",
    answer: "Aladdin",
    options: [
      "Aladdin",
      "Titanic",
      "Frozen",
      "Aquaman"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Who played Edward in the Twilight film?",
    answer: "Robert Pattinson",
    options: [
      "Taylor Lautner",
      "Robert Pattinson",
      "Andrew Garfield",
      "Ryan Gosling"
    ]
  },
];